Martin, Albert, Papers /3051
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Model "Construction Safety Program" Preface, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Safety Program for Construction Stone and Webster, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Source of Injuries Report, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Monthly Summary of Injuries, Accident Report Summary, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Job Safety Analysis, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Citation Number 1 Appearing in "Employers' Compensation Liability for Physically Handicapped Workers," The Ten Axioms of Accident Prevention, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Ethics + Economics Property Duties (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Readings in Ethics and Economics, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Christian Ethics and Moral Philosophy, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Basic Christian Ethics, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Social Responsibilities Business J.A. Fitch Organized Labor H. Bowen (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Handicapped Employees, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Incoming Letters, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Personnel Forms and Records, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Benjamin Selerman - Ethics of Business, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- John M. Galbrath - The Concept of Countervailing Power, 1952-1958 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Labor Union History From Labor In America, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Unfinished Readings in Economics (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Readings in Economics + Ethics (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Ethics in the History of Economics (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Ethics in the History of Economics (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Readings in Ethics and Economics, 1950-1952 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Absenteeism and Turnover, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Induction + Job Training Employees Education, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Personnel Administration, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Apprentice Training, 1952-1956 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Statistics U.S.A., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Internal Revenue Regulations, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Techniques of Interviewing, The Counseling Interview, 1951-1957 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Improving Your Interviewing Skill in Fact- Finding, Language and Vocabulary in the Interview (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Techniques for Motivating the Respondent, Student Poll Graphic, Employment Interview Graphic (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Errors of Reporting in the Interview, Interviewer Bias in the Employment Interview, Motivation in the Interview (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Tips on Employment Interviewing, Suggestions for Interviewing, Evaluation of Interviewing Techniques (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Pertinent Sections of the Taft- Hartley Act, Shop Employees Job Rating: Factors and Degrees, The Fog Index (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Points Assigned to Factors for Interview (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Use of Questions, Employee Rating Report, Salary Rating Specifications- Clerk- Typist Class D, 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Industrial Sociology Chapters 1-6, Spaulding Text Quiz (Box 15, Folder 9)
- The Coffee Case: Arbitration Decision- North American Aviation Inc., Los Angeles International Airport and UAW, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- The Coffee Case: The Incident and Assignment+ Attachments (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Performance Rating Instruments, Letting Employees Know How They Are Doing, Suggestions for Use of Employee Rating Report (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Office Routine Chart and Rating Forms (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Nation's Business July 1960, Basic Test of a Wage and Salary System (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Notes (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Wage and Salary Reports and Articles, 1956-1963 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Automatic Voting Machine Corporation Job Classification Summary, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Application and introduction of the Job Rating/ Evaluation Plan, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- "Job Evaluation During the Postwar Era" by Eugune J. Benge and Salary Rating Plan from 1962 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Job Evaluation Personnel Policies Forum and "What's Wrong with Job Evaluation", 1954-1956 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Points Assigned to Factor Degrees and Range for Grades (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Discussion and Company Position on Stock keeper Evaluation, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Job Evaluation Substantiating Data (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Summary Appraisal- Management Inventory and Development (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Papers and Reports on the Merits of Job Evaluation (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Job Analysis: Mutual Telephone Company (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Employee Rating/ Merit Review Records and Rating Plans (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Case Studies on Job Evaluation and Effectiveness (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Patterned Merit Review Forms and Interview Forms, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Performance Appraisals (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Role Playing Cases: Discussing Unsatisfactory Efficiency Ratings, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Wage and Staffing Schedule Pamphlets (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Executive Compensation Reports and Surveys, 1953-1957 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Problems with Job Evaluations, 1957-1960 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Training and Reference Manual for Job Analysis, Guide for Use of NEMA Job Rating Manual, 1944-1946 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Misc. Job Evaluations and Report (Box 15, Folder 36)
- NMTA Wage and Salary Administration Bulletin No.3 Parts I-X, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Principles of Manpower Building, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Wage and Salary Reports and Articles, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Employee Benefits and Compensation: Time Off With Pay, Vacation, Severance etc., 1952-1956 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Lecture Outline and Notes: Incentive Compensation (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Controlling Capital Expenditures, "The Effective Supervisor: An Organization Research Study", 1953 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Interview Form (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Employees' Financial Problems, Nonsupervisory Office Employees, Employee Rating for Production, Maintenance and Service Personnel, News Clipping, 1951- 1955 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- ILR 361 Papers: Union Viewpoints on Job Evaluation- Jack Stieber; Evaluating Managerial, Supervisory, and Staff Jobs- Wells Marshall (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Purposes of Incentive Wages, Time Study and Suggestion Plans, Wage- Salary Administration- Personnel Policies Forum, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Welch Allyn Inc. Employee Rating Chart, General Appraisal Report (Box 15, Folder 48)
- Employment Application City Delivery Drivers, "Lease or Purchase"- Fred Muth (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Automatic Voting Machine Corporation Job Analysis Sheet (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Miscellaneous Job Evaluation Related Materials (Box 15, Folder 51)
- Cornell Management Workshop Series Announcement and "Plan for Manual", 1962 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Line - Staff Obsolete, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Human Relations: Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Teaching Methods, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Training Apprentices Through ICS A Proposals, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Dartnell Left-Dev. Courses, 1948-1952 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Adult Training A Recommend Procedures (Box 16, Folder 6)
- A Recommend Procedure for Supervision Training (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Role Playing (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Case for Benevolent Autocracy, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- The Meaning of Human Relations, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Reorg. Without Crisis, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Letting Employees Know (Box 16, Folder 12)
- What Employers Expect, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Notes on Manual Efficiency (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Admin. Change: Outline (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Professor William F. Whyte, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Motivation: job Satis., Productivity 2, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Misc. Business Management, 1955-1958 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Delegation, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Multiple Management, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- D - 613, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Principle of Manag. Delegation, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Principles of Management, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- 0 - 374, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Principle Management Central, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Organization, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- 57-3094, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Product Planning, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Ives Conf. Prep., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Manual Conf. Lead (Emerson), 1947 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Discipline, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Conference Leadership, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Conference Leadership Practice Discussions American Airlines, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Line and Staff in I.R., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Span of Defeat, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Control Means Action, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Presiding: formal Meetings, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Mgt. Functions, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Misc., 1954-1965 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Employee Tests, 1955-1959 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Improved Selection, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Outline of Personnel Tests, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Safety: Use of Chemicals, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Mag. - Occupational Hazards, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Machine Guarding, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Course Acc. Prevention Manual, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Home Safety (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Accident Investigation and Analysis, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Safety and Top Management, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Safety Contests, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Safety: Housekeeping, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Cartoons, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- State Safety Programs: Wisconsin, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Safety Programs: Policy Statements, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Safety: Organization of Safety, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Safety: Organization of Safety (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Company Safety Program: Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- 2nd Injury Law, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Hicks: Life Ind. Relations., 1941 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Hicks: life Ind. Relations., 1941 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Personnel Relations (Decentr.), 1956 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Exit Interview, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Music in Industry, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Tests: Psych. Corp., 1957 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Cartoons, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Policy Manual Supervisors, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Personnel Audit, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Stock Plans, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Reading Racks, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- R.I.A. Awards (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Personal Administration: Duties, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Minimum Wage Laws, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Personnel Policies, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Social Security, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Credit Unions, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Bulletin Boards, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Making Charts, 1942-1951 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Veterans' Re-employment Rights, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Plant Relocation, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- A. S. T. D. - I. T. C., 1957 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Memory Improvement (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Profit Sharing, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Construction Tests, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Automation, 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Counseling in Industry, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Protective Labor Legislation, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Office Equipment (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Recruitment, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Scholarly Books in America, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Wiley Catalog, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Washington Fall Books, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- McGraw-Hill Books in Business and Economics, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Survivor Benefit Plan, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Disability Benefit Plan, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Group Insurance for Employees and Annuitants, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Employees Thrift Plan, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Economics Books McGraw-Hill, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Industrial Bulletin, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Business and Industrial Management Books McGraw-Hill, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Political Science History and Sociology Books, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Praeger Paperbacks Books that Matter, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Paperback Books - The University of Chicago Press, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- 1964 College Texts (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Books for Colleges and Universities, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Books for Colleges and Universities, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Skin, Hide and Leather Defects (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Harvard Divinity Bulletin, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- McKay College Catalog, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Industrial Relations, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Survivor Insurance, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Bibliography Cases and Other Materials for the Teaching of Multinational Business, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Talk, Work, and Action, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Employee Rating (Shop), 1951 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Training Manual for Interviewers and Observers, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Human Relations Training, 1947-1953 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- American History Atlas (Box 19, Folder 28)
- name - Report to the Membership, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- The Importance of Prestige, Training Responsibility and Pay in Developing Better Foremen, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Executive Communication - American Management Association, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Human Relations in Management, 1947-1949 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Exercises and Problems in Price Theory (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Handbook on Women Workers, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Employment Interviewing, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Your Personnel Management, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Handbook for Edison People, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- The Foreman's Basic Reading Kit (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Democracy and the Gospel of Wealth Amherst College Studies, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Ethics in a Business Society Child's + Cater, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Christianity and Property fletcher (Box 19, Folder 41)
- R.H. Tawney Econ. + Ethics - Religion and the Rise of Capitalism (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Biblical Faith and Social Ethics E. Clinton Gardner, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Christian Ethics (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Executive Communication Course Unit No. 2, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- Executive Communication Course Unit No. 3, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 46)
- AMA Exec. Common Reports (Follow-up on Course), 1958 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Industrial Communications, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Communication, 1956-1960 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Visual Aids, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Oral Communication, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- H 334, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Address on Labor Problems 1960 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Planning for Course in Labor Economics, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Preparing for Collective Bargaining - 2, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Preparing for Collective Bargaining - 2, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Econ. News Clippings, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Plan of Group Insurance Benefits, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- The National cash Register Company Adding Machine Division, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Battle for the Hospitals, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Affluence, Collective Bargaining and Steel, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Area Employment Statistics, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Where Management Development Belongs, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Case Studies, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Labor Law Labor Reporting, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Labor Law, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Training Methods in- Baslet Sensitivity Gaming, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Misc., 1960 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Need for Training: Address, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Train Execs. While Work, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Union Outlook M.D. (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Management Development: Brake Shoe, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Westinghouse Office Methods, 1954-1957 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Gen. Areas Ind. For. Outlines (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Personal Planning, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Handling Grievances, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Hospital Admin., 1954 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Group Manag. - Ansul Plan, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Management Controls, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Mgt. Analysis of Preg., 1957 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Management Education: History, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Filmed in Case M.D., 1950 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Empathy: Need of Mgt., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- The Exec. Neurosis, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Too Much Man - Too Little Change (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Attitude Surveys, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Self - Taught M.D., 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Fog Index Paragraphs, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Notes on Industrial Relations News, 1958-1960 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Insurance Benefits for Workers in the State of New York, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Industrial Relations News, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Disability Benefits - Workmen's Compensation Board (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Notes and Employee Relations Bulletins (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Agreement - Governing Wages, Hours and Working Conditions -Between- Columbian Rope Company Auburn, N.Y., 1961 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Introduction to Public Relations, 1950-1951 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Labor Policy and Practice Bulletin to Management, 1956-1962 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Claims Guide for the Employer, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Industrial Relations News, 1958-1961 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Community Relations: Being a Good Neighbor, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- New York State Job Patterns, U.S. Labor Supply and Mobility in a Newly Industrialized Area, 1960-1970 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Employee Relations in Action Man & Manager, Inc. "Labor Union History and Administration" Part A: Labor Union History- James Morris, ILR 352, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Why You Act as You Do?, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Human Relations, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Employee Relations Bulletins, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Training and Research in Industrial Relations: 2, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Women's Labor Law Pamphlets, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Training and Research in Industrial Relations, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Monthly Labor Review Feb. 1956, "Free Collective Bargaining Works!" General Motors UAW-AFL-CIO A Record of Progress, 1956-1961 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Agreements Between Morse Chain Company and Ithaca Machinists, Corning Glass Works and the American Flint Glass Workers' Union of North America, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Misc., 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Notes (Box 23, Folder 12)
- The Negro Revolution and Employment, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- News Clippings and Articles, 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Articles on Unions used in Dissertation, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Business 206 Hour Examination, White- Collar Employment and Income Articles, 1958-1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous, 1955-1965 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Free Collective Bargaining, 1948-1960 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Luncheon Speech "The Twilight Zone of State- Federal Jurisdiction"- Jay Kramer, Chairman New York State Mediations Board, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Monthly Labor Review Vol. 79 No.2, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- ILR Research Publications vol. VIII- IX, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Training Opportunities for Women and Girls, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Censored Agreement between Two Parties- For Educational Purposes?, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Corning Glass Works, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Labor Relations Pamphlets (Arbitration etc.), 1952 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Morse Chain Company, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Conference on Economic Security held May 11th- 13th- "Current Economic Problems and Trends- Earnings and Incomes" Speech by Robert H. Ferguson, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Careers for Women as Life underwriters, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Articles on Unemployment, 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- State Hour Laws for Women, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- "The Role of the Union in Contemporary Society" and the "Changing Role of Government in Labor Relations" (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Misc., 1955-1965 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- "A Solution to Union Monopoly Power," "Military Leave Policies," and "BNA's Labor Arbitration Reports", 1956-1963 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Preparation for Automation and Extension Programing, 1956-1958 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- "Economic Power and the Free Society," "Religion and Labor," "Organized Labor Chapter 1 An Introductory Statement", 1957 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- "New Areas of Collective Bargaining and the Public Interest: The Case of the United Federation of Teachers and the New York City Board of Education"- Dr. Charles Cogan, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Misc. Papers and Pamphlets, 1953-1962 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Social Legislation Bulletin and Industrial Bulletin, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- "Corruption and Racketeering in the Labor Movement"- Philip Taft, "Institutional Economics and Trade Union Behavior"- Campbell R. McConnell, 1955- 1958 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- "The Negro Revolution and Employment"- Eric Polisar, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Training and Research in Industrial Relations, 1945-1947 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- "Industry- Wide Bargaining"- Leo Wolman, "Why You Act As You Do," "Human Relations in Small Industry", 1954 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Unemployment and Disability Benefits Pamphlets, 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Agreement between Columbian Rope Company and Local 1085 Textile Workers Union of America, 1950-1961 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Addresses by Under Secretary of Labor W. Willard Wirtz and Secretary of Labor James P. Mitchell, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Commissioner and Deputy Commissioner of Labor Statistics, Ewan Clague and Robert J. Myers, Respectively, on Automation's Effect on Labor and Society, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- "Emerging Economic Issues in Labor- Management Relations" Convocation Address by Ewan Clague, Commissioner of Labor Statistics, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- "Hiram Insurance Company" Case Study and Employment Interview Graphic, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous Reports, Papers and Articles, 1956-1961 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Summary of Labor Arbitration Awards, "The Case for Boulwarism"- Hebert R. Northrup, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Journal Articles on Developments in Labor, 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Cornell University NYSSILR "New Issues in Arbitration," New York State Executive Department Commission Against Discrimination Publications, 1961- 1962 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- "Forum on Mental Health in Business and Industry," "Business in New York State," Ford Motor Company Annual Report, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Union Power and Labor- Management Relations, The International Operating Engineer, Steel's Competitive Challenge, 1959-1962 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- NAM Employee Relations Division "Some Facts About The AFL-CIO Merger," General Electric Public & Employee Relations News: What About Pay Increases Which Starve Recovery and Feed Inflation, 1956-1958 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- "Unions and Union Leaders of their Own Choosing," "AFL-CIO Codes of Ethical Practices," "Why Living Costs Keep Creeping Up." What the Multi-Billion Dollar Labor Merger Means to Industry, 1955-1960 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Stanford M.D. Plan, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Training: Professional Soc., 1953 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- M.D. Programs on Panaceas Miracle Dawgs, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Report Works; Use Sentence, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Identifying Promot. Exec's, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Foreman - Key to Morale, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Pre - Management Training Programs, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Org. of Training, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Discussion Leadership, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- New Employees: Adjusting + Coaching, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Creative Thinking, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Single Copies of File, 1954-1956 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Misc. NYSSILR, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Conference Leadership, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Supervisory Training, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Economic Dev. USA 1963 N.Y. Times Economic Review (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Economic Development India, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Org. Structure Outlines for Notes (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Industrial Relations News, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Employee Education, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Employment of Youth, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- B.N.A. Daily Labor Report, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- NYS Anti-Discrimination Commission, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 4)